[Music] Let's see, let's
[Música]
see, I'm coming to see how it
a ver a ver me estoy viniendo a ver com
's still giving a lot to talk about, eh,
está dando mucho que hablar todavía eh
I like Juanca's hit better, no no no
Me gusta más el hit de juanca no no no
no, but Comanche is breaking it down,
no pero Comanche lo está partiendo las
things as they are
cosas como son
when when he draws you a picture, the SS,
cuando cuando te hace un dibujo el SS
Okay, you're popular when the
Vale Eres popular cuando el canciones
sad songs 66 draws you, yeah,
tristes 66 te hace un dibujo sea es que
I'm crazy because they only funnify me
estoy loco porque me funen solamente
so he can draw me a picture, the Sas are the
para que me haga un dibujo el Sas son el
seasoning. Hey, what is it, what is it, this
sazón Oye qué es lo que qué es lo que es
thing about being able to donate 10 members, I
eso de que se pueden donar 10 miembros
don't know what you told me on
no sé qué que me habéis dicho en
telesalseo, but I don't, I don't understand, I don't
telesalseo pero yo no me yo no me entero
understand, I don't understand what this
yo no me entero yo no me entero de qué
is about, Comanche has gone a little bit, he has
va la movida se le ha ido un poco la o
gone a little bit, he has let go behind the
al Comanche sí se le ha ido un poco a ha
wheel, he has simply let go behind the
solto al volante simplemente ha solado
wheel. I'm coming, he has let go behind the
al volante me estoy viniendo ha solto al
wheel and he goes, he goes where he goes, he goes
volante y y va va para dónde va va sin
aimlessly, he goes aimlessly, but
rumbo va sin rumbo va sin rumbo pero
sson already did one for comch in sud, like this. Let's
sson ya le ya le hizo uno a comch en sud
see, this is
di así a ver este es perreando
basically perreando this is a  little dog this is
básicamente esto es un perreito esto es
a little dog
un perreito
okay the other time he drew it the other
vale la otra vez que lo dibujó la otra
time he drew it what was Javier This is
vez que lo dibujó qué era Javier Esta es
the cookie funa Oh how good
la funa de las galletas Uy qué bueno
this one How good how good this one is very good
este Qué bueno qué bueno este buenísimo
This was the other one Look let's see clearly the
Este era el otro Mira a ver claro el
topic the topic the topic the topic let's see there are a
tema el tema el tema el tema a ver hay
lot of people who are having debates
mucha gente que está haciendo debates
about the topic of Comanche It's not that I
sobre el tema de Comanche No es que no
can't put C where Javi Put down the
puedo poner C donde Javi Suelta la
guitar XD Tell Comanche to do a
guitarra XD Dile a Comanche que haga un
remix of Javi er is a judge lalisa has
remix de Javi er es juez la lalisa tiene
an ass that I want to eat it lalisa
un toto que se lo quiero comer la lalisa
has an ass that I want to eat it I
tiene un toto que se lo quiero comer se
want to let it go damn ma that ass
lo quiero soltar [__] ma ese totito
is big babe I want to [ __ ] you in
está grandote mamacita quiero darte por
the ass that you have Go mu
el culoe que tienes Dale mu toto Dale
toto Go move that ass Go move that ass Go move that ass Go move that ass move that ass move that ass Go go move that ass Go move toto up down up
mueve el toto Dale mueve el toto Dale
down is her
to to arriba abajo arriba abajo está su
tit How delicious her delicious her how delicious her how
teta Qué rica sua rica sua qu rica sua
delicious her is
qu rica está sua dale
come on mommy mother I'm [ __ ] good that she is really hot that she has an ass okay perfect straight to Amarillo let's see there is a lot there is a lot of debate with the Comanche issue it is giving a lot to talk about and it is fighting it is fighting with half of Twitter Comanche right now
en estos momentos
okay
vale
Well there are a lot of people calling him a dog there
Bueno hay mucha gente llamándole perro
are not many people calling him a dog but I
no hay mucha gente llamándole perro pero
don't understand why he is fighting with
no entiendo por qué se está peleando con
Twitter with Twitter Spain in particular I
Twitter con Twitter España en concreto
don't understand why Why in conc
No entiendo el Por qué Por qué en conc
ostia This was great This was
ostia Esto fue buenísimo Esto fue
great dude It turns out they put
buenísimo chaval Resulta ser que ponen
this clip of me calling a girl on the
este clip mío llama a una chica por
phone and look
teléfono y mira
manche Hi I mean luares ate This
manche Hola o sea luares se comió Este
bite okay because the girl mentions
bite vale porque la chica menciona
manche and I was thinking luares let's see I
manche y pensaba luares a ver yo me lo
thought about it too but why did they put
pensé también pero porque me pusieron
the click here it's not my fault tell me
aquí el click yo no tengo culpa
and of course it was a coincidence that
dime y claro era era la casualidad de
the girl mentions Comanche she
que menciona la chica lo de Comanche
mentions Comanche and then there's a guy over
menciona Comanche y luego hay un tío por
there making suspicious moans not
ahí haciendo gemidos sospechosos no
behind the phone so we
detrás del teléfono entonces nos
thought it was Comanche but the
pensábamos que era Comanche pero coge la
girl takes it and denies it okay kiss Yolanda
chavala y lo desmiente vale beso Yolanda
welcome beautiful take Yolanda no
bienvenida guapa coge Yolanda no De
where did I just get that her name is
dónde me acabo de sacar que se llame
Yolanda from somewhere I just got that her
Yolanda de alguna parte me acabo de
name is Yolanda Oh no Yolanda
sacar que se llame Yolanda Ah no Yolanda
is the one who donated this one is called
es la que ha donado esta se llama a
yulin what could it be Yolanda she looks like
yulin que podría ser Yolanda se parece
Hi this was a joke we made days
Hola esto era una broma que hicimos días
before all this happened Boom okay
antes de que pasara todo este Boom vale
Sorry we always make jokes that they
Perdón siempre hacemos bromas de que
call a streamer And at this moment
llaman a streamer Y en este momento
we said a man without knowing what I would do
dijimos un hombre sin saber qué haría
Javi You didn't tell me Happy birthday I'm
Javi No me dijiste Feliz cumpleaños ya
not going to donate to you again angry face No
no te vuelvo a donar cara cabreada No
man donate to me brendy happy birthday do
hombre dóname brendy feliz cumpleaños
you want me to dedicate a song to you
quieres que te dedique una canción
brendy tremendous Javi but I don't know
brendy tremendo Javi pero es que no sé
how h or rather this is supposed to be a
cómo lo h o sea se supone que esto es un
clip from days ago before the funa and
clip de hace días antes de la funa y a
this click reaches it somehow I
le llega este click de alguna manera no
have no [ __ ] idea why but oh
tengo ni [__] idea del por qué pero
well I imagine that someone would be
bueno Me imagino que alguien lo estaría
putting it on Twitter or whatever okay
poniendo en Twitter o lo que sea vale
Total that chikia a little
Total que la chikia un timing un poco
weird timing well nothing happens it desm between
rarito bueno no pasa nada lo desm entre
the girl the cli and I get this  the pipa I've been
la chica el cli y me llega este el pipa
looking at Who was and is
que he estado mirando Quién era y es
Raquel a kiss pipa okay And it's like the
Raquel un beso pipa vale Y es como el
anug but under budget I mean I'd be
anug pero debajo presupuesto O sea ya me
screwed I'd be screwed okay an anug but
jodería ya me jodería vale un anug pero
under budget a kiss a kiss
de bajo presupuesto un beso un beso
guys Thanks guys Javi oliveira
chicos Gracias guapos el Javi oliveira
this is a boxing journalist a far-
este es uno de box periodista de extrema
right journalist spouts more hoaxes than words the
derecha suelta Más bulos que palabras el
[ __ ] So I start looking around a
cabrón Total que me pongo a mirar un
bit and it turns out that he handed me
poco y resulta ser que me puso en
such a sasca on a silver platter because it
bandeja tremendo sasca porque es que
turns out that the guy eh the one who's
Resulta ser que el tío eh el que me está
accusing me of being a far-
acusando de ser un periodista de extrema
right boxing journalist and who spouted more hoaxes
derecha de box y que suelto Más bulos
than words had to beg
que palabras le tuvo que pedir perdón de
Cristina Seguí's forgiveness on his knees because she
rodilla la Cristina seguí porque se
believed that hoax that the
comió el bulo ese que estaba poniendo la
far-left was putting out precisely the
extrema izquierda precisamente los
Podemos media to
medios de comunicación podemitas para
throw [ __ ] at Cristina Seguí and this
tirarle [__] a Cristina seguí y este
clown just to throw [ __ ] at
payaso solamente por tirarle [__] a
Fran cua took the article Ah Cristina
Fran cua cogió el artículo Ah Cristina
Seguí uploaded the video of two minors
seguí subió el vídeo de de dos menores
being abused or being raped I don't
siendo abusadas o siendo violada no me
remember no and it's like Ah perfect without further ado go [ __ ] yourself
acuerdo no y es como Ah perfecto sin más
you know that was
a tomar por el culo sabes que eso
also done by someone that you all know  that had to be
también lo hizo uno que todos sabéis que
good I don't remember if he picked up
tuvo que bueno no me acuerdo si recogió
cable or went for adante and okay Javi what do you
cable o tiró para adante y vale Javi qué
owe Box but uncle Mira says to him
le debes a Box pero el tío Mira le dice
Cristina I spread a video of a
Cristina yo difundí un vídeo de una
minor being brutally raped, I mean
menor siendo violada brutalmente o sea
Look what the guy posted eh Look what
Fíjate lo que puso el tío eh Fíjate lo
the guy posted that he had to delete it
que puso el tío que lo tuvo que borrar
Thanks your twi is certified I'm going to
Gracias tu twi está certificado te voy a
crush you with all certainty literally
crujir con toda seguridad literal
Cristina is reporting everyone who
Cristina está denunciando a todo el que
is saying That that barbarity I mean
está diciendo Esa esa barbaridad o sea
but you have an interview on the
pero es que tenéis una entrevista en el
utbh Channel where she shows everything and
Canal de utbh donde lo muestra todo y lo
talks about everything without any kind of problem
habla todo sin ningún tipo de problema
yes but if it's the one from Comanche don't dedicate it to me
sí pero si es la de Comanche no me la
face rolling with laughter
dediques cara revolviéndose de la risa
kiss a kiss brendy Thank you very much I mean
beso un beso brendy Muchas gracias O sea
you have an interview with Cristina on the
tenéis una entrevista de Cristina en el
utb Channel where she tells everything
Canal de utb donde lo cuenta todo
perfectly, I mean Cristina what she did
perfectamente o sea Cristina lo que hizo
was publish on her Twitter account
fue publicar en su cuenta de Twitter una
a censored video with the
un vídeo censurado con las caras
pixelated faces of some girls who had
pixeladas de unas chicas que habían
accused some boys a few days ago of
acusado hacía unos días a unos chicos de
raping them and the girls on their
de violarlas y las chicas en su cuenta
Instagram account were  saying that it
de Instagram estaban diciendo que todo
was all a lie that they were going to be on TV
era mentira que iban a salir la tele
Haha let's go on TV it's all a
Jaja vamos a salir la tele todo es
lie So Cristina took that
mentira Entonces Cristina cogió ese
video from the girls' account that I
vídeo de la cuenta de las chavalas que
think the account had like 8 or 10,000
creo que la cuenta tenía como 8 o 10,000
followers I don't know something like that and Cristina
seguidores no sé algo así y Cristina lo
uploads it okay but Cristina is
sube vale pero que Cristina se lo está
asking for it the prosecutor's office the crime okay And well there's
pidiendo la fiscalía el delito vale Y
another thing going on but I'm not
bueno hay otra movida por ahí pero no me
going to get into that I'm not going to get into
voy a meter en eso no me voy a meter en
that okay but look at it in
eso vale pero miradlo en el vídeo de
utbh's video There you are it's
utbh Ahí os
not the excerpt This but it's very
no es no es el extracto Este pero es muy
strong it's a very strong thing okay And there are
fuerte es una movida muy fuerte vale Y
people who are spreading the boo
hay gente que está difundiendo el buo o
either because of ideology or to throw
bien por ideología o bien por tirarle
[ __ ] at Fran Cuesta okay at least he
[__] a Fran cuesta vale al menos
rectified within the toxic Chernobyl doesn't arrive no
rectificó dentro de lo tóxico no llega
no Of course he rectified
chernóbil no no Claro él rectificó
because this is a It's that this is
porque es que esto es una Es que esto es
a lawsuit that I lost you know that there is no you
una demanda que pierd ya sabes que no
know that no I mean you know the
hay sabes que no O sea sabes Ya el
result because there are lawsuits that you
resultado porque hay demandas que tú
say Well let's go to trial we
dices Bueno vamos vamos a juicio
fight I have told you this you have
peleamos Yo te he dicho esto tú me has
told me but this is a lawsuit  since you already
dicho pero esto es una demanda ya que tú
know in advance what the
sabes ya De antemano Cuál es el
result is Hi Cristina sorry for the
resultado Hola Cristina siento el
inconvenience I deleted the
inconveniente he borrado el tweet
important tweet I just read in my tweet it is
importante Acabo de leer en mi tweet se
understood it says I just read that in my
entiende dice Acabo de leer que en mi
tweet it is understood that Cristina Seguí
tweet se entiende que Cristina seguí
published a video of a woman being
publicó un vídeo de una mujer siendo
raped and it is
violada y no es así se entiende se
not like that it is understood it is understood no [ __ ] that you posted it it is understood no that you posted it okay Although she did spread a video of the woman being raped questioning her status as a victim no no no questioning the questioning
víctima no no no poniendo el poniendo en
the status of victim it was not a
duda la condición de víctima no era un
video but the video It is on
vídeo pero es que el vídeo Está en el
Cristina's Twitter if I'm not mistaken it
Twitter de Cristina si no me equivoco
was a video in which the girls said they had
era un vídeo en el que las chicas decían
lied or rather you freak out and there is
que habían mentido o sea flipas y está
the one with the knife giving it to Cristina
el de faca dándole caña a la Cristina
continue with this and there is the other one on the
seguir con esto y está el otro el de la
motorcycle and it's like but man but yes it is yes it
moto y es como pero tío pero si está si
is oh the tweet if it can be verified and
está ah el twit si se puede comprobar y
there you see a little of the
ahí pues ves tú un poco los tinglados
media rackets that are put together the
que se montan mediáticos las
media cancellations that they try to
cancelaciones mediáticas que intentan
do you know but it makes me laugh eh  it is
hacer sabes pero me hace gracia eh se se
understood I just read that on my tweet I
entiende Acabo de leer que en mi twit
just read Because while I
Acabo de leer Porque mientras que
wrote I have not realized what I have
escrito no me he dado cuenta de lo que
written you know I just read my husband does
he escrito sabes Acabo de leer mi marido
not stop screaming Francisco Javier help
no deja de gritar Francisco Javier ayuda
kiss Give him a hug Yolanda your husband a
beso Dale un abrazo Yolanda tu marido un
kiss a genius but well anyway there are
beso un genio pero bueno en fin hay
some who do not back down or ask for forgiveness
algunos que ni reculan ni piden perdón
eh There are some who do not ask for forgiveness there are
eh Hay algunos que no piden perdón hay
some who have like
algunos que tienen como
eh Like that ego that you are telling him
eh Como ese ego que le estás diciendo
man apologize that I sue you apologize
tío discúlpate que te demando discúlpate
that I am going to report you and and they have like
que te voy a denunciar y y tienen como
that pride with their shitty community
ese orgullo con su comunidad de [__]
knows toxic and it's like my god get
sabe tóxica y es como madre mía meterte
into a mess get into a mess eh for
en un jaleo meterte en un lío eh por
someone who is not with you or anything man
alguien que no va contigo ni nada tío
okay I mean and this guy Oh I could swear that they
vale o sea y este tío Ay juraría que
put the photo of the turkey here to
pusieron por aquí la foto del pavo para
show you who it was but come on that
enseñaros quién era pero vamos que me
guy gives me that with all his face You Javi
pone el tío eso con toda la cara Tú Javi
did you know that Cristina and Roma do not
sabías que la Cristina y el Roma no se
get along Yeah yeah I know man a
llevan bien Sí sí lo sé hombre hace
long time ago but well what do I do Javi another
tiempo pero bueno qué hago Javi otra
visit to the court another lawsuit they are going to
visita al jugado otra demanda te van a
become a VIP member no Albert in this case
ser miembro VIP no Albert en este caso
no  I have nothing to do with it Ali shut his
no tengo yo nada que ver Ali le cerró la
mouth a few days ago look and he also deleted
boca Hace unos días mira y también borró
the tweet What the [ __ ] I went into
el tet What the fuck he entrado al
Franco's live and attacked him I hope
directo de Franco y lo ha atacado Espero
you're okay and the guy takes it and had
que estés bien y coge el tío y había
posted something had posted something against
puesto algo había puesto algo contra
Fran look and says to lesbi man if you
Fran mira y le dice a lesbi hombre si tú
don't want him to be okay that's your problem
no deseas que esté bien es tu problema
pinado or rather you go and know what he posted
pinado o sea vete tú a saber lo que puso
that he deleted the tweet he would surely post
que borró el twi seguramente pondría
something Wishing wishing that the servant
algo Deseando deseándole que el siervo
had killed him or some move like
lo lo hubiese matado o alguna movida de
that I mean characters characters anyway
esa o sea personajes personajes en fin
the moror the moror has given him some stick
el moror el moror le ha dado cañita
Comanche says and seeing what's happened with
Comanche dice y visto lo visto con
Comanche I'm right again for a
Comanche vuelvo a tener razón para
change depression xdd more like
variar depresión xdd más bien retraso
mental retardation and lack of attention there are a lot of
mental y falta de atención hay mucha
people who are claiming that the
gente que está afirmando que que el
fact that he waits let's see about the
hecho de que espera vamos a ver lo del
millor first that the fact that com that
millor primero que el hecho de que com
the fact that Comanche is
que el hecho de que Comanche la esté
causing trouble pardis it means that the
liando pardis significa que los
mental problems that they claimed
problemas mentales que alegaban que no
were not true and I think that
eran verdad y yo creo que no tiene nada
one thing has nothing to do with the other I mean
que ver una cosa con la otra O sea no
the speed has nothing to do with the
tiene nada que ver la velocidad con el
cough or rather for me one thing doesn't take away
tosino o sea para mí una cosa no quita
the other I don't know if this will be part of
la otra no sé si esto formará parte de
an outbreak or something like that or is it her
un brote o algo por el estilo o es su
personality I think it is her personality
personalidad creo que es su personalidad
eh because they sent me some clicks today they
eh porque me mandaron hoy unos clicks me
sent me today on Instagram a girl
mandaron hoy en instagram una chica
others c that I think I don't think that they are not
otros c que creo que no creo que que no
going out there much let's see I
están saliendo por ahí mucho a ver yo
only ask this
solo le pido a este
2024 to bring me a girlfriend eye Look
2024 que me traiga una novia ojo Mira
manifest look look eye I put on
manifesto mira mira ojo me puse calzones
red panties look
rojos mir
no a it can be seen that they are Calvin Clay cuos
no a se ve que son Calvin Clay cuos
How many of you in the chat want a partner can you see
Cuántos del chat queréis parej se ve
How many in the chat Yes true from the chat
Cuántos del chat Sí cierto del chat
How many want a new partner okay There
Cuántos quieren parej nuevo vale Ahí
ask for a girlfriend Here it starts then
pide una novia Aquí empieza entonces
here Start asking for the characteristics
aquí Empieza a pedir las características
of the girlfriend don't tell me to look for
de la novia no me digas que busques a
a big ass Look for someone that
una culona Busca alguien que te
complements you Of course a big ass
complemente Claro pues una culona lo
complements it Yes that is what it has to
complementa Sí eso sí es que tiene que
then I would tell you Don't tell me that you are looking to
entonces te diría No me digas que bus
fit in I mean that it fits all your
encajar me refiero que encaje todos sus
p after everything that has happened of course
p después de todo lo que ha pasado claro
not a a companion not a travel yes I think I think let's
no una una compañera no de viaje sí creo
see if you find the right
Creo que a ver si encuentras a la
person I think that  yes that
persona adecuad creo que sí que te
could work for you Yeah that's what it has to
podría funcionar Sí eso sí es que tiene
then I would tell you Don't tell me to
que entonces te diría No me digas que
look for a big ass Look for someone
busques a a una culona Busca a alguien
who complements you Sure, well, a big ass
que te complemente Claro pues una culona
complements him Oh [ __ ], what does it come first eh Let's
le complemento Ay [__] qu es antes eh A
see commitment no but I'm
ver compromiso no pero ya estoy
ready I mean commitment is
dispuesto o sea compromiso es
committing to getting married no I mean not
comprometerte a casarte no O sea no
commitment to having something serious with Sure
compromiso de tener algo serio con Claro
but that's something different and today I finally
pero eso es algo diferente y hoy por fin
decided that I want there some
ya me decidí que ya quiero ahí una
tranquility tranquility like now already
tranquilidad tranquilidad as ya ya
leave it what it was already leave the
dejarla lo que era ya dejar la vida de
crazy life Okay yes yes yes but but like that I hope hopefully
loco Okay sí sí sí pero pero así Ojalá
we're going to change the word
ojal vamos a cambiar la palabra
commitment for stability Comanche of
compromiso por estabilidad Comanche de
not going of Not being a rascal
no ir de De no ser picaor
noando there as I know him a little bit
noando ahí yo como lo conozco un poquito
quite a bit in fact eh and I see you
bastante de hecho eh y que te veo
calm down in your life like Well, what I
tranquilize en tu vida en plan de Bueno
see more is that what he's missing, I
yo más que lo veo yo creo que que le
think that's what he's missing
hace falta creo que es lo que le falta
for it to finally fit together, by fitting together
para que termine de encajar con encajar
I mean for all its pieces to fit together
me refiero de que encaje todas sus
after everything that's happened of
piezas después de todo lo que ha pasado
course not a travel companion I think let's
claro no una compañera no de viaje Creo
see if you find the
que a ver si encuentras a la persona
right person I think that it could work for you  that's what
adecuad creo que s que te podría
someone has to understand is that at some point he
ent alguien es que ahí en algún momento
told him that as a requirement he wanted her to
le le ha dicho que como requisito quería
be a big ass that's why Paul
que fuera una culona por eso el Paul le
is telling him man don't tell me a
está diciendo hombre no me digas que una
colony tell me a travel companion not
colona dime una compañera de viaje no
a big ass new girl I'm not going to be unfaithful
una Nova culona no le voy a ser infiel
because that's where I'm going to have her the opposite would
porque ahí la voy a tener lo contrario
make you very happy but it's that you know what
te hace muy feliz pero es que sabes qué
I feel if I have a big
es lo que yo siento que si yo tengo una
ass girlfriend I'm not going to be unfaithful
novia culona no le voy a ser infiel
because that's where I'm going to have her there she's going to be
porque ahí la voy a tener ahí va a estar
with me Believe me believe me luckily
conmigo Créeme créeme que por suerte la
life takes many turns Because later if I do
vida da muchas vueltas Porque después si
n't have a big ass new girl I'm going to see a big
no tengo una nuev culona voy a ver una
ass girl and she
culona y se me
leaves me she has to be big ass okay so I don't
va tiene que ser culona vale para que no
cheat on her let's see
le ponga los cuernos a ver vamos a ver
what the best one says Ah okay I've
qué le dice el millor Ah vale Ya ya lo
seen it dude it sounds very low m this doesn't
visto tío se escucha muy bajo m esto no
follow me wants to be my girlfriend and doesn't
me sigue quiere ser mi novia y no me
follow me Lisa has a nice ass the truth is he
sigue la lisa tiene buen culo la verdad
So he whispers I don't know I don't know I don't know dude
el Así que susurra no sé no sé no sé tío
sincerely I think that each person has to
sinceramente yo creo que cada persona ha
know a little bit how far to go You
de saber un poco hasta dónde llegar
know I think that some friend should have
Sabes Yo creo que algún amigo le debería
told Comanche  that he looks for a
haber dicho a Comanche que busque
job man that he tries hard in other
trabajo tío que se esfuerce en otras
things Comanche is not going to save his
cosas Comanche no va a salvar su
situation I'm serious it's not negative it's not
situación va en serio no es negativo no
bad people think like oh wow
es malo gente se piensa como que Oh Wow
he quit social media I've failed
he dejar las redes sociales he fracasado
in life no, I'm just as worthy to
en la vida no yo es igual de Digno a
work in any other thing just as
trabajar de cualquier otra cosa igual de
worthy like it's even better you're going to
Digno en plan es incluso mejor vas a
have 1 times better quality of life it's going to
tener 1 veces mejor calidad de vida va a
be so much better what are you trying to
ser muchísimo mejor qué intentas
achieve man you have to talk that's
conseguir tío tienes que hablar es
correct I'm speaking how I have to
correcto estoy hablando como tengo que
speak and how I have to speak is how
hablar y como tengo que hablar es como
I decide to speak not like you are going to
yo decido hablar no como tú me vas a
tell me that I speak [ __ ] Because I speak however I feel like
decir que yo habl cabrón Porque yo hablo
something that you can't do
como se me da la per gana algo que tú no
why Because you're a
puedes hacer por qué Porque eres un
poor son of a [ __ ] you're [ __ ] I
pobre hijo de laa tú eres una [__] O
mean you're writing this and you're a
sea tú estás escribiendo esto y eres un
poor piece of [ __ ] okay I can but it's that
pobre de [__] okay yo pued pero es que
this of this of I mean I don't understand the
esto de esto de o sea yo no entiendo el
point when Comanche starts saying
punto de cuando Comanche se pone a decir
this about you are a poor piece of [ __ ] I don't know
esto de tú eres un pobre de [__] no sé
what I don't know how much I can do or so
qué no sé cuánto yo puedo hacer o sea
why does he go on about sides the other
por qué se pone en plan lados el otro
day I looked at him and he has 200 subs on Twitch and I
día lo miré y Tiene 200 subs en Twitch y
think as viewers  he's having
de espectadores creo que anda teniendo
100 200 300 I don't think he has anything like that I
100 200 300 No creo que tiene algo así O
mean he's not a millionaire let's say he'll earn the
sea no es millonario vamos cobrará el
minimum wage in his country maybe I don't
sueldo mínimo de su país a lo mejor no
know what he's referring to I think this is
sé a qué se refiere yo creo que esto es
a joke I'm not Yolanda's husband
una broma no soy el marido de Yolanda
Francisco Javier Oliveira don't manipulate
Francisco Javier oliveira no manipules
okay By the way Every day I stop by
vale Por cierto Cada día me paso por
where she climbs to leave my dislike a
donde la trepa para dejar mi dislike un
kiss handsome Thank you very much Javi with
beso guapo Muchísimas gracias Javi con
manche he's not well he's not cured anymore
manche no está bien no está curado ya
but let's see but do you think this is
pero a ver pero creéis que esto forma
part of an outbreak do you think this is
parte de un brote creéis que esto es
irony because of course then on Twitter I
ironía porque claro luego en Twitter
also saw that a few
también he visto que hace unos cuantos
years ago he goes down the street and records a
de años va por la calle y graba una
woman and says mm white meat I don't know if you
mujer y le dice mm carne blanca no sé si
've seen that on Twitter I mean I
habéis visto ese por Twitter o sea yo
think this is part of his
creo que esto forma parte de su
personality And the truth is that he's terrible
personalidad Y la verdad que está fatal
as a Mexican as a Salvadoran
como mexicano como salvadoreño
Puerto Rican Argentine I don't care
puertorriqueño argentino me da igual por
why because I have enough money
qué porque tengo el suficiente dinero
to make any settlement and it's worth it
para hacer cualquier asento y me la pena
On the other hand you don't That's the difference between
En cambio tú no Esa la diferencia entre
you and me that you go to your [ __ ] job
tú yo que tú vas a tu fucking trabajo
that's the problem that he has it's
ese es el problema que tiene es
literally what I was talking about
literalmente lo que estaba hablando
Someone has  explain to this man that
Alguien ha explicarle a este señor que
working is not something bad it is not something
trabajar no es algo malo no es algo
insulting it is not something to be
insultante no es algo de lo que sentirse
ashamed of you can't think of
avergonzado no puedes plantearte las
things like that Hello boss how are you Good morning
cosas así Hola jefe qué tal Buenos días
then you have to speak
entonces tú tienes que hablar
politely every day no [ __ ] I don't
educadamente toos días no cabrón Yo no
I can as I please Why
yo puedo como se me la gana Por qué
Because I am rich because I am a millionaire you
Porque soy rico porque soy millonario tú
are not an [ __ ] you
no eres cabrón
are an [ __ ] and that is something that you never I
t es cabrón y eso es algo que tú nunca
believe that it is like that you are going to get to
yo creo que es así vas a llegar a ha
like me he put strong strong plan
como yo ha puesto fuerte fuerte plan
strong Comanche does not have 10000 euros in the
fuerte Comanche no tiene 10000 eur en la
bank account did you see what Fran cuesta does
cuenta del banco viste lo de Fran cuesta
Yes I saw what Fran cuesta does he
Sí he visto lo de Fran cuesta se ha
hooked up with Felipe again Fran
enganchado otra vez con Felipe Fran
cuesta Seriously Holy [ __ ] do you equal I don't
cuesta En serio Holy shit igualas no
want Yes now we are going to see what
quio Sí ahora lo vamos a ver lo de
Felipe does, gossip a lot I want above all I
Felipe salsear mucho Quiero sobre todo
want to play LoL a little bit
quiero sobre todo jugar al LoL un poco
man I have played very few games
tío que me he jugado muy pocas partidas
yes Anica But within the Euphoria that
sí Anica Pero dentro de la Euforia que
can have due to the polarity within
puede tener por la po aridad dentro de
that he gets euphoric that is always
que se ponga eufórico eso siempre está
related to sexual issues and that
relacionado con temas sexuales y esa
filth and those lack of respect no
guarrerías y esas faltas de respeto no
because I was even telling him this
porque incluso estaba diciéndole est
disrespecting the husband of one
faltándole respeto al al marido de una
of them since the beginning of the season but yes
de ellas desde empezar la season pero sí
Comanche is going to have a very very
Comanche va a tener una vida muy muy
sad and very miserable life unfortunately
triste y muy miserable desgraciadamente
if he thinks that the only way to feel
si cree que la única forma de sentirse
successful is to dedicate himself to
exitoso es dedicarse a las redes
social networks because he is not going to be able to do it the
sociales porque no va a poder hacerlo el
only chance he had and that he had was
único chance que tenía y que tuvo era
good somehow he managed to
bueno de alguna forma consiguió
suck [ __ ] to get to a
comiendo pollas llegar a una situación
relatively relevant situation in a
relativamente relevante de forma
surprising way but right now they are going
sorprendente pero es que ahora mismo van
to deny him I mean do you think that
a renegar de él es decir te piensas que
your Play is going to give more hype to
aur Play le va a dar más bombo a
Comanche for these things no it is not true it
Comanche por estas cosas no ni es verdad
is true Rubius none of these
es verdad Rubius ninguna de estas
people are going to give him more hype with
personas le va a dar más bombo con lo
which even when they were giving him hype he had
cual incluso cuando le daban bombo tenía
four people watching it You know So I don't think I don't think he has
cuatro personas viéndolo Sabes Así que
absolutely
no creo no creo que tenga absolutamente
any kind of future comancha I think he
ningún tipo de futuro comancha creo que
should look for a job or study
debería buscar trabajo o estudiar
either of the two Okay but let him
cualquiera de las dos Está bien pero que
do something with his I am a woman on the internet
haga algo con su soy mujer en internet
thrown all Christ but one thing is to
tiado todo Cristo pero una cosa es
do it privately and another thing is to
hacerlo por privado y otra cosa es
do it publicly no Also what value does it
hacerlo por público no Además Qué valor
have is how coman will flirt in a non-
tiene es como coman ligará de forma no
ironic way like you will flirt with
irónica en plan tú te liaras con
Comanche I mean it's literally like
Comanche o sea es literalmente como
when
cuando
eh is  literally Like when someone
eh es literalmente Como cuando alguien
on the street it's something that I've never
por la calle es una cosa que yo nunca he
understood uh I think I have super
entendido eh creo que tengo vídeos super
old videos talking about street harassment
antiguos hablando de acoso callejero
when the typical
cuando los típicos
uh apes stand on the street they're not
eh simios se ponen por la calle no están
in a group and a girl who's
en grupo y pasa una muchacha que está
okay walks by and starts pretty blonde I'll eat your
está bien y empieza rubia guapa te como
[ __ ] it's you know not the typical
el [__] es sabéis no el típico acoso
street harassment no I've never understood that I mean
callejero no que yo nunca he entendido
but neither me nor being me kani
eso o sea pero ni yo ni siendo yo kani
or boy or anything It bothers me that has
ni chaval ni nada Me incomoda eso me ha
always bothered me because it's like let's see
incomodado siempre porque es como a ver
one thing is that you get a little mad
una cosa es que tú te pongas un poco
They're affections they're no in the end I let's
melos Son cariños son no al final yo a
see now we have the internet now we have
ver ahora tenemos internet ahora tenemos
such there are many times that uh
tal hay muchas veces que las eh
social relationships work in
relaciones sociales pues funcionan de
a way in which you at work or
una forma en la que tú en un trabajo o
in a place you meet a woman or you know
en un lugar conoces a una mujer o sabes
and whatever comes up but literally it would
y surge lo que sea pero literalmente
n't have anything
tampoco tendría por qué tener nada de
wrong with you seeing a person on the street that
malo que tú veas por la calle a una
you like and there are ways to
persona que te guste y hay formas de
politely try to approach them No maybe
educadamente intentar acercarte No a lo
there's a person that you see
mejor hay una persona que tú vas viendo
on the street constantly not in your
por la calle constantemente no por tu
area or whatever and one day they come and say
zona o lo que sea y llega un día y dice
Hey look I'm sorry I don't know what I know  you do it to
Oye mira Perdona no sé qué yo que sé
talk you do it to crash no uh
haces por hablar haces por chocar no eh
exchange words no and see if he can
intercambiar palabras no y ver si puede
is stick his neck in a little bit It's
es meterle el cuello un poquito No pasa
okay because of that okay but him him
nada por eso vale pero el el
literally him being an ape I mean
literalmente el el ser un simio o sea el
on the street and that still exists today
por la calle y eso existe a día de hoy
uh him on the street a
todavía eh el por la calle que vaya una
girl who's well looking goes and grabs a guy with
muchacha que esté bien y coja un tío con
a belly like Donkey Kong and
una panza como Donkey Kong y le
says to her pretty he'll eat you and it's like why are you
diga guapa te comía y es como Por qué
doing that I mean do you think the girl is going to
haces eso o sea crees que la chica se va
turn around and [ __ ] you or
a volver y te va a [__] o sea
whatever the thing no why
cualquiera de las cosas no del porque
because it bothers no I mean why do you do
porque incomoda no O sea Por qué haces
that do you think that because you call someone
eso crees que porque tú llames a alguien
like they're a yoide they're going to turn around
como si fuera un youride se va a volver
and give you their phone number I don't know I don't
y te va a dar el teléfono no sé no lo
understand no and he ate you how [ __ ] disgusting what the
entiendo no y él te comía que que [__]
[ __ ] are you going to eat me disgusting
asco qué [__] me vas a comer asqueroso
cannibal what the [ __ ] are you going to eat me Go
caníbal qué [__] me vas a comer Vete a
suck it it's not like I've never never
chuparla no es como nunca nunca he
understood that Of course you
entendido eso Claro tú las cosas las
do things with a purpose not when you
haces con un propósito no cuando tú le
're hitting on a girl on
estás tirando fichas a una chica por
Twitter on the internet or whatever  you do it
Twitter por red o lo que sea lo haces
with the intention of flirting not
con la intención de m de ligar no de de
trying to flirt But you're yelling
intentar ligar Pero tú le estás gritando
at a person on the street as if
a una persona por la calle como si el
human beings didn't walk on all fours anymore, I
ser humano no andase a cuatro patas ya o
mean, what do I know? It's like I don't understand. You
sea yo que sé es como no lo entiendo no
're not crazy. Comanche with that
está flipados El Comanche con esa
attitude is going to sink into [ __ ],
actitud se va a hundir en la mda
humility, work, and respect That's the
humildad trabajo y respeto Esa es la
basis to get somewhere in life. Of course, of
base para llegar a algo en la vida claro
course, a kiss, you know, he
claro un besoo sab es que literalmente
's literally making a fool of himself right
com está haciendo el ridículo ahora
now. One thing is that you have
mismo una cosa es que tú tengas un
hot content, okay, hot content, and you
contenido Hot vale un contenido Hot y
talk about sex one night with your
hablas de sexo una noche con tus
followers or even the song
seguidores o incluso lo de la canción
that's cringe-inducing. But it could be humor, it could
que de cringe Pero puede ser humor puede
be a joke that he has on his channel,
ser un cachondeo que tenga en su canal
okay. But I think it's his personality that he's
vale Pero creo que es su personalidad lo
doing, eh. I think I think that's
que está haciendo eh Creo que creo que
him, like sometimes he talks to me on
ese es él como alguna vez me habla por
DM, but it's like, what's the fun in flirting
md pero es como qué gracia tiene ligar
with someone who flirts with everyone, I
con alguien que liga con todo el mundo o
mean, That's my perspective That's my
sea Esa es mi perspectiva Esa es mi
perspective, like, how come
perspectiva como anch ha tirado por md
you threw Princessa on DM? What's the fun in flirting
tú a Princesita qué gracia tiene ligar
with someone who flirts with everyone,
con alguien que liga con todo con todo
Christ, no, you have no idea  of the
Cristo no ch no os hacéis una idea de la
amount of streamers that have hit
cantidad de streamers que me han tirado
on me on DM I mean I never say anything eh
por md O sea que yo nunca digo nada eh
but you would be really surprised I mean I
pero os sorprendería muchísimo es decir
never say anything because
nunca digo nada porque pues
obviously I'm not going to say this guy
evidentemente no voy a decir este pibe
hit on me on DM this guy
me ha tirado por md este pibe me ha
hit on me on DM no but he has never
tirado por md no pero os nunca lo ha
said it He has never said princess to anyone
dicho Nunca ha dicho princesita a nadie
who has hit on him yeah ever if he has
que le haya tirado sí alguna vez si ha
said any it would be surprised have you
dicho alguno ser sorprendería hablaste
ever talked to osl yeah I never met
alguna vez con osl sí que nunca quedé
him or did anything with him like a lot of
con él ni hice nada con él como mucha
people think because I don't know let it be if he
gente se piensa porque no sé djelo de s
said it if he said it he says it when
lo ha dicho s lo ha dicho lo dice cuando
the topic is viral well into there luar
el tema está viral bien metido ahí luar
eh well into eh and automatically
eh bien metido eh y automáticamente todo
everyone thought that I had slept
el mundo se pensaba que yo había follado
with him I didn't talk to him I mean he
con él no hablé con él O sea me
answered my stories he didn't get
respondía historias él a mí no llegó a
anywhere with me because I think he asked me to meet up
nada porque creo que me dijo de quedar
sometime and he said Paula no way don't
alguna vez y me dijo Paula ni de coña no
meet up with him and I was like okay anug
quedes con él y yo como vale anug le
said Paula no way don't meet up with him
dijo Paula ni de coña no quedes con él
of course the nug seeing herself in the
claro la nug viéndose en la situación
other's situation anug seeing herself in  the situation
del otro anug viéndose en la situación
of what was the name of the pouf I'm sorry
de cómo se llamaba el el puf Lo siento
baby I'm sorry Yes anug is a SIM I don't
nene lo siento Sí anug es un SIM yo no
think it's a SIM I think it's an Obvious you
creo que sea un SIM creo que es un Obvio
know some at some point it has come
ya sabéis alguno en algún momento ha
up to say some for x reason
surgido el decir alguno por x motivo
but
pero
what have they told you well it depends on who it
qué te han dicho bueno depende de quién
depends on who The truth is that I
depende de quién La verdad es que a mí
don't like to hang out with streamers much, I
no me gusta lgar mucho con streamers es
mean except for one
decir excepto por una persona en
specific person I've only gone out with one streamer So to
concreto solo he salido con un streamer
speak I mean I've never
Por así decirlo es decir nunca he
been I'm not one to hang out with streamers in
estado no soy de estar con streamers en
general it's like I don't like him I don't like him it's
general es como que no me Mola el no me
like it's not true that ger
Mola el es como que no es cierto que ger
Romero hit on you no Romero not by luck or
Romero te tiró no Romero no por suerte o
misfortune but that would surprise more than
desgracia pero que sorprendería más de
one because I've even been hit on by
uno porque incluso me han tirado
streamers who had a girlfriend that's
streamers que tenían novia eso me ha
happened to me too and it's been a bit like
pasado también y ha sido un poco en plan
What the [ __ ] that the truth is you would do
What the fuck que q la verdad te harías
to Juan de Dios no the truth is I've done the
a Juan de Dios no la verdad te he hecho
complete opposite to you I mean Juan de Dios
todo lo contrario es decir Juan de Dios
No complete
No todo lo
opposite What's wrong with an that someone
contrario Qué le pasa con an que alguien
[ __ ] with an
se [__] con an por
please please someone that someone
favor por favor que alguien que alguien
[ __ ] [ __ ] like please
se [__] conche como por favor
rescue him the only way to get him out of
rescatarlo la única manera de sacarlo de
there is for someone  put out that fire
ahí es que alguien apague ese fuego por
please someone [ __ ] Comanche
favor que alguien se [__] Comanche
lower your [ __ ] livid lower your
bajarle el putísimo lívido bajarle el
[ __ ] livid What's wrong with you Comanche
putísimo lívido Qué le pasa Comanche De
Really Oh my God someone take out your
verdad Oh my God que alguien le saque la
[ __ ] please I can't take it anymore I can't take it anymore I can't take it
lefa por favor no puedo más no puedo más
anymore it's all the time TV is
no puedo más es todo el rato tele de com
horny I'm not volunteering I
salido no me ofrezco voluntaria yo no
'm not a tribute from my District okay I can
soy tributo de mi Distrito vale Yo pued
look like a Mexican as a Salvadoran
haar como mexicano como salvadoreño
Puerto Rican Argentine I don't care
puertorriqueño argentino me da igual por
because I have to talk like I'm
porque tengo por habla como si fuera el
John Chimy man because he talks like I'm
John chimy tío por habla como si fuera
Bad Buny because like I'm J
Bad buny porque como si fuera J
Chimichangas uncle young chimichurri I don't
chimichangas tío joven chimichurri no lo
understand because he doesn't talk like llados
entiendo porque no es habla como llados
mico this guy it doesn't matter it doesn't matter We don't
mico este tío da igual da igual No le
criticize him It's that he's the [ __ ] he can do what
criticamos Es que es la cra que puede
you're right he
hacer lo que que tienes razón es que
can do whatever you want he's the
puede hacer lo que quieras que es la
goat man no ironically he's the goat
cabra tío no irónicamente es la cabra
Din Uy but he doesn't follow me he doesn't follow me he
Din Uy pero no me sigue no me sigue
wants to be my girlfriend and he doesn't follow me the
quiere ser mi novia y no me sigue el
best he's the best he's the best he's the best he's
mejor que es el mejor que es el mejor
got a good ass
tiene buen culo
right he's the goat he's the
verad es que es la cabra es que es la
[ __ ] Cab I mean if  100,000 viewers
[__] Cab O sea si se 100000 viewers
psycho man watching chicks on Instagram
psicom manche viendo a tías en Instagram
and saying wow she has tits she doesn't
y diciendo vayas tetas tiene no se
deserve 100,000 viewers and man he's already
merece 100.000 viewers y hombre ya ya ya
had 100,000 viewers so how many
ha tenido 100000 viewers o sea cuánta
people have seen how many people have
gente habrá visto cuánta gente habrá
seen this clip so far Well look at nothing more
visto ya este clip Pues mira nada más
than nothing more than the tweet has 3
que nada más que el twit tiene 3
and a half million like the tweet uh
millones y medio de o sea el tweet eh
this tweet that orlock is seeing has
este tweet que está viendo orlock tiene
3 million impressions uh watching I
3 millones de impresiones eh viendo
have my dick up who deserves it who
tengo la pija parada quién se lo merece
really deserves it me or so
quén se lo merece de verdad yo o sea
Honestly uh I didn't want to I mean I didn't want to
Honestamente eh no quería O sea no
talk about Comanche or I'm being honest I did
quería hablar de Comanche o soy sincero
n't want to talk about Comanche because
no quería hablar de Comanche porque
basically 4 months ago he uploaded a video
básicamente hace 4 meses subió un vídeo
hita 4 months ago or five whatever it was I
hita hace 4 meses o cinco los que fueran
uploaded a video basically saying that
subí un vídeo básicamente diciendo que
the hate comments were going to make them commit
los comentarios de hate iban a hacer que
suicide and it was like Wow like okay okay
se suicidas y fue como Wow o sea vale
Hey when did yel Melo come back to Twitch
vale Oye cuándo volvió yel Melo a Twitch
let's go okay okay we take a step back
metemos vale vale damos Un paso atrás
you know what I'm saying but my [ __ ] mother
sabes lo que te digo pero mi [__] madre
but he's lost his mind I love him
pero es que ha perdido la cabeza lo amo
dude he's the best he's literally  the
tío es el mejor es literalmente el
man sined The man who sold the
hombre sined El hombre que vendió el
world the man who sold Twitch eh
mundo el hombre que vend Twitch eh De
Really what an outrage dude I love him I love him I love him
verdad qué barbaridad tío lo amo lo amo
he's the best guy
lo amo es el mejor tío
sex seal sex sexal sex
sex seal sex sexal sex
sexal the other day I was watching a
sexal el otro día estaba viendo como una
jeeva
jeeva se me
approach me the other day I was watching
acercaba el otro día estaba viendo como
a jea
una jea se me
approach me this big ass has a really
acercada esta culona tiene una teta bien
badass tit I don't know what I'm going to do I want to
cabrona Yo no sé qué voy a hacer quiero
give her anal sex sexoal sex sex an sex
darle sexo anal sexoal sexo sex an sex
[Music] I
[Música]
should make one with comche for
debería hacerme un con comche por lo
what good music he's the best he has the
quea buena música es el mejor tiene la
ca I mean I didn't want to make
ca yo o sea no quería hacer membres de
Comanche members I mentioned him once but I didn't
Comanche lo mencion alguna vez pero no
want to make Comanche members or
quería hacer membres de Comanche ni
his conip because what I tell you how many
conip suyos porque que os digo hace cu
months ago when he had I don't know when
meses cuando tuvo no sé cuando de
suddenly the whole internet hated him It's that I
repente todo internet lo odiaba Es que
don't know I don't understand much the
tampoco s O sea no entiendo mucho la
controversy of coman I understand that they
polémica de coman entiendo que lo
hated him I don't know why he was in series and
odiaban no sé porque estaba series y
because he hung out with streamers a lot I don't
porque se juntaba mucho con streamers No
know exactly what the tone was But
sé exactamente Cuál era el tono Pero
well upload a video so that I understand that the
bueno subid un vídeo que entienda que la
majority the truth is that I don't know  nor
mayoría la verdad es que no sé tampoco
because they hated him at the time because
por lo odiaban sea en su momento porque
sex is that Hey but he also has his
sex es que Oye pero también tiene su
talent with manche eh sexanal sexal sexanal I
talento con manche eh sexanal sexal
mean I'm not capable eh I'm not
sexanal o sea yo no soy capaz eh yo no
capable of doing it eh you saw saying
soy capaz de hacerlo eh visteis diciendo
that he was crazy, I
que que estaba mal de la cabeza o sea en
mean like he had depression and
plan que tenía problemas de depresión y
anxiety problems and that all the
ansiedad y que todos los comentarios de
hate comments had taken him to the point of
de hate le habían llevado un punto de
almost committing suicide and it's like Well although I
casi suicidarse y es como Bueno aunque
want to say regardless of how
quiero decir al margen de cómo le caiga
each one feels about manche okay or so
cada uno con manche vale o sea
let's respect okay Well not me because I did
respetemos vale Bueno yo no porque yo yo
n't say anything bad about Comanche I don't but
no dije nada mal de Comanche Yo no pero
even from the outside I saw it and I said Okay okay I mean
aú desde fuera lo vi y dije Bueno vale o
calm down let's respect now you can Grab
sea calma respetemos ahora ya pued Agar
the meme because yesterday m Ángel was
el meme porque ayer m Ángel estuvo
commenting on it for 4 hours straight live
comentándolo 4 horas seguidas en directo
saying Comanche every 3 seconds and today
diciendo Comanche cada 3 segundos y hoy
before opening the chat he was talking
antes de abrir el chat estaba hablando
about Comanche the whole time but everyone is
de Comanche todo el rato pero está todo
talking about Comanche with these
el mundo hablando de Comanche con estos
c How many viewers is this not bringing him
c Cuántos viewers no le está trayendo
viewers
viewers esto
1.600000 followers Mm what's up the
1,600000 seguidores Mm qué va los
last two live streams the last two live
últimos dos directos los últimos dos
streams have had more  more visits no no there
directos han tenido más más visitas no
are a few here you can also
no aquí hay unos cuantos también podéis
look at me Let's see how many viewers you're
mirarme A ver cuántos viewers está
having let's see Twitch Tracker Twitch
teniendo a ver Twitch Tracker Twitch
Tracker com It has 200 subscribers 257 subs
Tracker com Tiene 200 subs 257 subs
Stream let's see January 2024 a peak of 286
Stream a ver enero 2024 un pico de 286
viewers The other day it had a peak of
espectadores El otro día tuvo un pico de
489 what's going on man the viewers no the
489 qué va tío los espectadores no los
viewers you're not increasing them I mean I don't
espectadores no los estás subiendo o sea
even know if he'll charge
yo es que no sé ni siquiera si cobrará
per tweet eh with those numbers let's see they're
por twit eh con esos números a ver son
the numbers basically that
los números básicamente que tenemos
we have on Twitch not 300 200 and I
nosotros en Twitch no 300 200 y yo ya
can already let's go how much do I have on Twitch
puedo vamos cuánto tengo yo en Twitch
What's going on here 86 subscriptions I have
Qué pasa aquí 86 suscripciones tengo yo
on Twitch and about 200 viewers there are no
en Twitch y unos 200 espectadores no hay
days that maybe 200 300 400 well we
días que a lo mejor 200 300 400 bueno
could say that we have an average
podríamos decir que tenemos una media
more or less like Comanche on
más o menos como la de Comanche en
Twitch eh but a little less subscribers I'll
Twitch eh pero un poco menos de subs yo
tell you what I charge on Twitch let's go
os digo lo que cobro en Twitch vamos
eh 300 Maybe 300 Maybe there is
eh 300 A lo mejor 300 A lo mejor hay
a month that you charge 400  500 of these
algún mes que cobras 400 500 de estos
months that maybe you're a little bit
meses que a lo mejor se te va un poco
more into, you know. That's why I'm telling you. So this
más sabes Por eso te digo O sea que este
man, well, well, but he doesn't live in
hombre bueno claro bueno Pero vive en
Mexico, but come on, I don't know if he earns a
México no pero vamos no no sé si gana
very good living, but it's just that he's
para vivir muy bien pero es que es
incredible. Comanche has been around for three months. Comanche has been around
increíble Comanche hace TR meses
for three months, eh. Please don't
Comanche hace TR mes eh Por favor no me
tell me ugly things, it'll kill me. Comanche, the
digan cosas feas que me mato Comanche la
news and how I have to talk is
actualidad y como tengo que hablar es
how I decide, how I, how I am, how are you?
como yo decido como yo como yo cómo está
Good morning, you have to tell your boss. Good morning, [ __ ], what's
jefe Buenos días cabrón que
up, I mean, in parentheses, no hate, he's
pasa o sea entre paréntesis no hate de
really the best, I love him, man, really,
verdad es el mejor le amo tío de verdad
and he does this with, does this literally
y hace esto con hace esto literalmente
with 200 viewers, he's the best, I
con 200 viewers es que es el mejor es
love him, man, I mean, literally, he's a
que lo amo tío o sea literalmente es un
free man, man, he's a
hombre libre tío es un hombre
completely clear man, with 200 viewers, man, it
completamente claro con 200 viewers tío
's what we all dream of one day, he'll give it a
es lo que todos espiramos algún día se
go. Nothing to lose, man, all day,
la pela Nada que perder tío todo el día
all day live talking about tits,
todo el día en directo hablando de tetas
[ __ ], asses, how his dick gets hard,
de [__] de culos de cómo se le para la
eh, in Mexico 300 isn't many, well, you
pija eh en México 300 no son muchos pues
know, give me members, [ __ ],
ya sabéis regalarme miembros cabrones
give me members and  subs leave me the
regalarme miembros y subs dejarme el
Prime okay I want to go to Mexico to
Prime vale que me quiero ir a México a
live Eh well well well how
vivir Eh bueno bueno bueno qué
crazy I love it I love it I love it I love
barbaridad lo amo lo amo lo amo lo amo
that ass you
de ese culo que me
sent me God I literally put you
enviaste Dios yo s literalmente te pongo
on all fours I spank you and I God it's that I
en cuatro te nalgueo y te Dios es que te
put it in you I put it in you very hard I really
meto te lo meto muy fuerte de verdad que
really prefer that first eh it's
prefiero de verdad que priero eh está
hot I mean it's Comanche
caliente o sea está El Comanche más
hotter than him in a bingo being 10
caliente que el en un bingo tener 10
years old and on Three Kings' Night breaking into
años y en la noche de Reyes meterme la
my parents' room and seeing my
habitación de mis padres y ver a mi
mom eating my dad's ass I
madre comiéndole el culo a mi padre de
really prefer that for 100
verdad que prefiero eso durante 100
times than a single clip of Comanche
veces que un solo clip de Comanche
talking about how he would [ __ ] a girl
hablando de cómo se cogería a una chica
on Discord really really really really how crazy How crazy How crazy How
por discord de verdad de verdad de
crazy I
barbaridad Qué barbaridad Qué barbaridad
'm not ready for this for
se no estoy preparado para esto de
real eh No ironically not only me
verdad eh No irónicamente no ya yo solo
but the people from TS Silos evangel we've
sino la la la gente del ts Silos evangel
also been TR for days Waiting
también llevamos TR cu días Esperando
for Comanche to open live because mother
que Comanche habra directo porque madre
of God we love to watch
de Dios noos encanta ver los directos de
Comanche's live shows and see what nonsense he's going to say
Comanche y ver qué barbaridad va a decir
today I really love him I love him he's the best he's the
hoy de verdad lo amo lo amo es el mejor
best what I believe and sorry I
es el mejor lo lo que creo y perdón aquí
'm here now a kiss handsome Roman I don't
ya me estoy un beso Román guapo no
want to act good I don't know I don't want to
quiero hacer de bueno no s no quiero
venture to say but I think now
aventurarme a decir pero creo que ahora
Com Manche is in his Chocas arc I think I think that's it
com manche está en su arco chocas creo
correct me if I'm
pienso que es eso corregidme si me
wrong I accept theories but I think that Ah
equivoco acepto teorías pero creo que Ah
Comanche after losing Heaven and
Comanche después de de perder Heaven y
Mother Base has entered like in the
mother base ha entrado como en el arco
Chocas arc you know and it's like he caught this
chocas sabes y es como ha pillado esta
attitude that now is like a bit of
actitud que ahora está como un poco de
fashion not because of Chocas but in general like
moda no por choca sino en general como
this attitude of I don't give a damn about anything I don't give a damn about anything
esta actitud de me suda la poya todo me
I'm the best eh I don't care
suda la [__] todo soy el mejor eh Me da
what they tell me I'm going to do my thing I'm the
igual lo que me digan voy a hacer lo mío
best I'm number one I'm rich you
Soy el mejor soy el número uno soy rico
know Well I don't know eh Chocas is from Vigo and
sabes Bueno no sé eh chocas es de Vigo y
Comanche from Claro guarand pii no I don't know I don't
Comanche de claro guarand pii no no sé
know where Comanche is the truth
no sé dnde es Comanche la verdad el
Chocas is from Vigo see I know he's Gallego
chocas es de Vigo ver Sé que es Gallego
but I don't know if he was from Vigo
pero no sé si era de Vigo
eh Let's see no  I know the guys are going that way or
eh A ver no sé se van por ahí los tios o
what, the truth is, I don't know if they're going that way,
o qué la verdad no sé si van por ahí los
mm I don't
mm yo no sé tampoco ni siquiera si es
know either, not even if it's a matter of an outbreak, the truth is, I couldn't tell you if it's a matter of an outbreak, if it's like I think, I think it's his personality, eh, I mean, regardless of the fact that I believe what he told us in the
de que me creo lo que nos contó en la
interview, no, and his suicide attempts
entrevista no y sus intentos autolíticos
and all that, I don't deny that, and that he has the
y demás eso no lo niego y que tenga los
disorders or has had those
trastornos o haya tenido esas
illnesses that he told us about, but I
enfermedades que que nos contó pero yo
think this is part of his
creo que esto forma parte de su
personality, I mean, he's like that, your physique,
personalidad o sea él es así tu físico
among other things, we have Juan
entre otro orden de cosas tenemos a Juan
S. Guarnizo, who has given his opinion on what's
s guarnizo el cual ha opinado de lo que
happening with Comanche, who wouldn't have
pasa con Comanche el cual no tendría
filters in his opinion with my [ __ ]
filtros en su opinión con mi [__] comi
crazy comi, I hadn't seen the whole mess.
loco no había visto yo todo el desmadre
Yesterday you guys were telling me in the
Ayer me estaban diciendo ustedes por el
chat, I don't know, I don't know what to tell you, today I spoke to him, no, he
chat no sé no sé qué decirles hoy le
hasn't answered me, I spoke to him
hablé no me no me ha contestado le hablé
tonight, I see him calm, let's
hoy en la noche yo lo veo tranquilo a
see Ari, I talk to him and he's calm,
ver Ari hablo con él y él está tranquilo
but I see him calm, I see him
pero yo lo veo tranquilo yo lo veo
calm, he says
tranquilo dice
Comanche Comanche  coming to telesalseo
Comanche Comanche viniendo a telesalseo
and leaving me with zero subs Juan Guarnizo
y dejándome con cero subs Juan guarnizo
Well, I see Comanche very calm,
Pues yo lo veo muy tranquilo a Comanche
eh, he's chill, eh, he's chill, he's chill,
eh está chill eh está chill está chill
Javi is, he's off his medication Yes,
Javi está él está sin medicamentos Sí
but being off his medication is within
pero el estar sin medicamentos dentro de
what it does to you, I don't know, within what it
lo que te haga No lo sé dentro de lo que
does to you and makes you go to another state and
te haga y te haga pasar a otro estado y
all that, but that type of comment about
demás pero ya ese tipo de comentario de
that heat, man, do you think that's part of
esa calentura tío creéis que forma parte
the outbreak? Yes, it was very unpleasant, the
del brote Sí fue muy desagradable los
clips are very cringy, yes, it has to be
clips s da mucho cring sí tiene que ser
something that I don't know, friends, no, I wouldn't
algo que no s no sé amigos no no sabría
even know what to think, you know that I
ni qué opinar les ustedes saben que yo
have a lot of affection for him, but
le tengo mucho cariño a él pero pues
obviously, I, there are things that don't
evidentemente yo yo hay cosas que no me
seem right to me And I saw that, it was very uncomfortable,
parecen Y eso lo vi fue muy incómodo
Gabriel. Thank you very much, handsome, I
gabrielo Muchas gracias guapo lo
needed it, eh, I needed it, Gabriel. A
necesitaba eh lo necesitaba gabrielo un
kiss, a kiss. Thanks for walking around here naked,
beso un beso Gracias por pasearte aquí
man. Here are the people. Look how he is
en pelota tío Aquí la gente Mira cómo
today, what can I tell you? The medication
está hoy qué te digo el medicamento lo
controls him without it, he becomes impulsive, I mean, of course,
controla sin él se hace impulsivo o sea
the impulsiveness of
claro le salta la impulsividad de las
things that he truly thinks about comes out, no, I
cosas que él verdaderamente piensa no O
mean, but is it his true self or is it not his
sea pero es su verdadero yo o no es su
true self, that's what I wonder, I
verdadero yo es lo que yo me pregunto
know  what I'm going to do
ya sé lo que voy a hacer se me acaba de
something just occurred to me Okay
ocurrir una cosa Vale se me acaba de
something just occurred to me let's see if I could
ocurrir una cosa a ver si me pudiera
come up with
salir una
something I wrote to a person if they
cosa le he escrito a una persona si me
answer me I'll tell you something okay I don't promise
contesta os digo algo vale no os prometo
anything yeah some
nada se se me acaba de venir un
content just came to my head for tomorrow but
contenido a la cabeza para mañana pero
little else I'm not going to come here to talk
poco más no voy a venir aquí a hablar
bad about my friend or anything like that because I
mal de mi amigo o algo así porque le
love him and it pisses me off because he was having a really good
quiero y me jode porque iba un muy buen
time quietly with his things with his
tiempo tranquilito con sus cosas con su
video with his tiktok with now with his
video con su tiktok con ahora con sus
live shows it pisses me off the truth it pisses me off a lot
directos jode jode la verdad jode mucho
but I do
pero
n't know look I don't know I would rather move on from the
no sé miren no sé preferiría ya pasar el
subject I don't know what to say Hoyos I could have seen
tema no sé qué decir Hoyos podido ver a
Chos explode just in case we come to you that Juan didn't
chocas explotar por si te vamos que Juan
want to get wet but basically he's saying that
no ha querido mojarse pero básicamente
what he's
está diciendo que que lo que está
doing with Manche is
haciendo con manche está dando
embarrassing comcha he said that
vergüencita comcha dijo que la
bipolarity makes him hornier than
bipolaridad lo pone más cachondo de lo
normal yeah let's see that's where my
normal sí a ver es que por ahí va mi
theory goes my theory goes because maybe
teoría mi teoría va porque a lo mejor
Juan is a person
Juan sea una persona
who [ __ ] let's see Juan not Comanche But I
que [__] a ver Juan no Comanche Pero
think it's obvious no that he won't have
creo que es evidente no que no tendrá
many sexual relationships and then he
muchas relaciones sexuales y entonces
always goes well you  I say very very
anda siempre pues ya te digo muy muy
naughty and Between that and the other it's a
salote y Entre eso y lo otro es un
cocktail that explodes,
cóctel que que explota
of course being an adult person who
claro ser persona ya adulta a al que le
likes women a lot and and and doesn't eat
gusten mucho las mujeres y y y no se
much, well he's going to come out, he's going to come out, he's going to come
coma mucho pues va a salido va a salido
out And if in Yes, of course a
va a salido Y si en Sí claro una persona
more or less normal person in a medium
más o menos normal en un medio se
controls himself but of course he can't be a
controla pero claro él no puede que sea
Virgo I don't think he'll ever be a Virgo
Virgo No creo que llegue a ser Virgo
but of course if you notice, always,
pero claro si os dais cuenta siempre el
uh, always like he's surrounded by
eh siempre como está rodeado de cosas de
jerk-off things, I mean, they called him to be a
pajas o sea lo llamaron para ser una
promo, uh, I remember an ad that
promo eh yo me acuerdo de un anuncio que
Comanche made for a company for a
hizo Comanche en una empresa de un
TV ad, let's say an
anuncio para la tele vamos un un spot
advertising spot and it was an ad about what
publicitario y era un anuncio de qué era
the ad was about learning English and
el anuncio de aprender inglés y el papel
Comanche's role was uh that he jerked off
de Comanche era eh que se hacía una paja
in the ad. Have you not seen that ad, let's
en el anuncio No visteis ese anuncio a
see if it's easy to find on YouTube?
ver si se encuentra fácil en YouTube
Comanche ad Look, Yes, of course it
Comanche anuncio Mira Sí claro que
appears on YouTube,
aparece en YouTube
look, a
mira un
kiss, he's hornier than
beso está más salido que la espalda de
a
un
hump's back, well, bird that
jorobo bueno pájaro que
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
fly
volá
[Music]
[Música]
sfr Blow your house as far as I know, Blow is
sfr Blow your house que yo sepa Blow es
a category on these pages but Blow
una categoría en estas páginas pero Blow
House that would be a bl  Here I'm
House eso sería un bl aquí
going to give you
te voy a dar
Okay with The goose in the hand the poor guy
Okay con El ganso en la mano el pobre le
has caught this eh Let's see I think that's
ha pillado esto eh A ver yo creo que va
the theme eh I mean I think it's
por ahí el tema eh o sea yo creo que va
a little bit about
un poco por
eh
eh
the the the heat that he has Okay says
la la la calentura que tenga Vale dice
Gibel do you want to see that video I have the
gibel quieres ver ese vídeo yo lo tengo
complete one what the porn video is the one you have you have
completo cuál el vdeo porno el que
the porn that he was watching
está tienes el porno que estaba viendo
with Manche let's see I think it's eh a
con manche a ver yo creo que es eh un
little bit the heat that he has and it
poco la calentura que tiene y ya se le
ends there with with the disorder it's it's that's where
termina ahí con con el trastorno sea es
the theme of course is it's a
que va por ahí el tema claro es es un
little bit of everything it's a little bit of everything everything that it is
poco todo es un poco todo todo lo que es
with Manche it goes there
con manche por ahí va por ahí
[Music]
[Música]
goes
va